Riccardo Fusiello

About me

Hi, I'm Riccardo Fusiello, I'm an ex student of the ITIS Sen.Onofrio Jannuzzi in Andria. I completed the five years of the ITIS in 2021 with a lot of great grades, particularly in the main subjects. Actually I'm studying Computer Science at University of Trento and my inspiration is to work in a great company of Computer Science or generally in a great company that invests in Computer Science and Innovation.

Personal Website: https://riccardofus.github.io/Cavi-Website/

Email: riccardo.fusiello02@gmail.com

Phone: (+39) 3895398639 Date of birth: 25/11/2002

Address: Via Pericle 120, 76123 Andria (Italia)

Working Experience

 $2023 - \dots$ Private lessons of science subjects with some students

 $10/05/2024 - \dots$ Automation of psychological tests with Google Suite

05/02/2024 - 29/03/2024 Machine Learning Internship at University of Trento

13/03/2023 - 29/03/2024 IT Service Desk at University of Trento

01/03/2022 - 15/03/2022 Full Stack Developer at Reply S.p.A, Remote

15/06/2020 - 15/09/2020 Full Stack Developer at Nuvité S.r.l, Andria

22/05/2019 - 07/06/2019 Vocational Training at Exprivia S.p.A, Molfetta

Education

 $30/09/2024 - \dots$ Master's Degree in Artificial Intelligence at University of Bari

17/09/2021 - 16/07/2024 Bachelor's Degree in Computer Science at University of Trento

15/09/2016 - 15/06/2021 Diploma in IT at ITIS Sen. Onofrio Jannuzzi, Andria (100L/100)

15/09/2019 - 21/06/2020 Certification on CCNA Routing and Switching: Introduction to Network of Cisco

15/01/2021 - 04/06/2021 Certification on Use and Programming of Comau Academy

Languages

Italian Mothertongue

English B1/B2, spoken every day and used to write sometimes

Programming Languages that I know:

C/C++, Java, Python, JavaScript, CSS, HTML, Arduino, SQL, Shell, Kotlin, Jetpack Compose

Personal Projects

Shelfy, libreria digitale a portata di mano

Autorizzo il trattamento dei miei dati personali, ai sensi del D. lgs. 196 del 30 giugno 2003